Transcript: spscriptorium Sync: John Smith - forom.com
I'm going out to South Park gonna have myself a time
Friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
I'm goin out to south park gonna leave my woes behind
Ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
I'm heading out to south park to see if i cant unwind
I like girls with big fat titties really big fat titties
So come on out to south park and meet some friends of mine
Episode 11x09 "More Crap" “巨屎记”
双语合成 Lv&daisy
恩，我可是相当确诊了 Mr. Marsh. 你这是便秘
Well, there's no doubt in my mind, Mr. Marsh. You are constipated.
谢谢告知这个我早就知道的消息
Thanks for the news flash!
最近三周，我还没有拉过一泡屎呢! 我只想知道为什么?!
I haven't taken a crap in over three weeks! The question is why?!
恩，你最近吃过什么东西? - P.F. Chang（美国著名中餐连锁）, 基本上，超赞的
Well, what food have you been eating? - P.F. Chang's, mostly. Good stuff.
那我给你开点泻药
I'm going to prescribe a laxative.
但是我必须警告你，当你最后拉下这坨屎的时候， 你可能会非常的疼
But I must warn you: when you do finally pass this stool, it might be very painful.
会有多疼呢？
How painful is "painful"?
上帝啊，终于要出来了
Oh God. Oh, here it comes.
哇，疼！疼！疼！疼！
Whoa, hot! Hot, hot! Whoa, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
终于结束了...终于结束了...
Oh, it's over. It's over.
天啊，人家现在感觉好多了
Oh God. I feel so much better.
哇！
Wow.
竟然可以这么大！
That is huge.
这肯定是有史以来我拉过的最大的一泡屎
That has got to be the biggest crap I've ever taken.
嘿，嘿 Sharon Sharon，你必须来看一下
Hey, hey Sharon. Sharon you gotta come see this.
Sha-Sharon?
怎么了，Randy? 你有什么... 欧, Randy!
What is it, Randy? Do you have any- Oh, Randy!
你瞧瞧? 这是不是你所见过的最大的一坨屎
Will you look at that? Is that the biggest crap you've ever seen or what?
看在上帝的份上，把厕所冲了！ - 拜托! 这可是件振奋人心的事!
Flush the toilet for Christ's sake! - Come on! That's pretty impressive!
嘿 Stan! Stan, 过来看看 - Randy!
Hey Stan! Stan, look at this. - Randy!
看看你老头干的 -这不可能!
Look what your old man made. - No way!
从来没见过比这坨大的，是吧? - 没有
Huh? Never seen one that big, have you? - No, never.
恶心, 老爸, 真恶心!
Gross, Dad, sick!
好了，现在能冲厕所了吗?! - 我将试一下，但是我不认为....
All right, will you flush the toilet now?! - I'll try, but I don't think...
等等，等等，我必须先打电话给Jimbo - 为什么?!
Wait a minute. I gotta call Jimbo first. - Why?!
他一定得看看这个.
He's gotta see this.
不，我们现在就要冲厕所！ - 不要嘛!
No, we are flushing the toilet right now- - No!
Jimbo必须看一下，这样我和别人说起的时候 他才能作证我不是在撒谎!
Jimbo has to see it so when I tell the guys how big it was, they'll know I'm not lying!
欧，看在上帝的份上, Randy! - Sharon, 这个很重要!
Oh, for the love of God, Randy! - Sharon, this is important!
Stan, 去打电话给你Jimbo叔叔. 我得在这守着
Stan, go call your Uncle Jimbo. I'm gonna stand guard.
嘿 兄弟们! - 嘿 Randy.
Hey guys! - Hey Randy.
你现在感觉好点了吗? - 恩, 我现在已经完全康复了
Are you feeling better? - Yeah, I'm totally fine now.
你们应该看一下Randy昨晚上拉的那坨屎!
You guys shoulda seen the crap Randy took last night!
我敢保证它是人类有史以来所拉过的最大一坨屎！
It was honestly, the biggest crap anyone has ever taken. Ever.
那个，有史以来不敢说...
Well I don't know about ever...
我告诉你们，这坨东西有像足球那么大
I'm telling you this thing was the size of a freaking football.
真的很巨哦
I guess it was pretty big.
一个足球? 真惊人！ - 我从没听说有这么大的
A football? That's amazing. - I've never heard of one that big.
噢, 我有个兄弟拉过一次很巨大的
Oh, my brother took a crap once, that was enormous.
大到可以载入世界纪录
It was the biggest in the history of the world, I think.
才没有我那坨大呢
It wasn't bigger than mine was.
没有，说真的，那坨便便绝对可以称为一怪兽
Oh no, seriously, this crap was a monster!
我的...我的更大
Mine... mine was bigger.
我表示怀疑
I doubt it.
你们想看一下吗？
You wanna see it?
哦，我的天啊！
Oh my freaking Lord.
它不可能是从你屁眼里出来的 - 它是的，是我拉的
That did not seriously come out of your ass. - Oh yes, it did.
走近点看看有没有裂缝 它是一个完美的整体
Go ahead and check it for splits. It's one solid piece.
上帝啊...
Jesus...
这个比你兄弟的大一点吧, Gerald?
That uh, a little bigger than your brother's there, Gerald?
根本就不是一个数量级的啊...
It's... other-worldly.
Randy, 你给吉尼斯世界纪录的人打电话了吗? 我说，真的有可能...
Randy, have you called the people from the Guinness Book of World Records? I mean...
这个真的是世界上最大的一坨屎!
this might seriously be the biggest crap in history!
这就是我悉心保护它的原因
That's why I gotta make sure to keep it safe.
Randy Marsh! - 哦，惨了!
Randy Marsh! - Aw crap!
你把那东西放在家里是什么意思?!
What the hell do you think you're doing keeping that thing in our house?!
他们和我意见一致, Sharon: 这坨便便可以载入纪录
The guys agree, Sharon: it could be a record holder.
为什么男人都能对自己的便便的大小非常在意?!
Why are men so obsessed with how big their crap is?!
这里是吉尼斯世界纪录美国分部? 有事需要效劳吗？
Guinness World Records America. How can I help you?
最大的屎?
The biggest crap?
我们根本没有这项纪录, 先生
We actually don't keep track of that record, sir.
因为我们不想去看
Because we don't want to.
我们一直接到有男人打电话来声称他刚拉了 世界上最大的屎
Look, we get calls from men all the time who believe they took the biggest crap
我们没有足够的人手去测量和核实
and we simply can't handle all the measuring and verification.
你必须打给在苏黎世的欧洲排泄物标准和测量中心
You need to call the European Fecal Standards and Measurements Office in Zurich.
不客气 Jeez，又一位便便狂
You're welcome. Jeez, another one.
吉尼斯世界纪录美国分部
Guinness World Records America.
是的，你好 我名叫Randy Marsh 我认为我拉了世界上最大的屎
Yes, hello. My name is Randy Marsh and I believe I took the world's biggest crap.
你必须打给位于苏黎世的欧洲排泄物标准和测量中心
You need to call the European Fecal Standards and Measurements Office in Zurich.
他们的电话有列在他们的网页上
Their number is listed on their Web site.
主席先生, 看一下这个 从美国寄过来的一坨屎
Herr President, take a look at this. It is a crap sent to us from the United States.
很不错啊
Very nice.
有被检测过真实性吗?
Has it been checked for accuracy?
从照片上来看不像作假
It appears to be legitimate, based on the photo.
我们估计这坨便便应该超过八又二分之一卡里克
We estimate that the crap is over eight and a half Courics!
我们最好现在就搭飞机
We'd better get on a plane. Right away.
有什么异样?
Hm, enshnusen?
没有什么
Verron snusunarich.
你拉这坨粪便前，最主要食物是什么, Mr. Marsh?
What was your primary diet for this poo, Mr. Marsh?
基本是P.F. Chang's. General Tsao's 鸡之类的
Mostly P.F. Chang's. General Tsao's Chicken.
每天早上还会吃很多Jemima的冻香肠和饼干
And a lot of Aunt Jemima's Frozen Sausage Biscuits in the morning.
我相信我检测到了一点卷心菜的残渣? - 哦，是的，我还吃了很多泡菜
I believe I detect some cabbage as well? - Oh yes, I had a lot of kim chee.
你们一定是在开玩笑吧
You have got to be kidding me.
这些人是从苏黎世来的， Sharon! 他们是欧洲人！
These guys are from Zurich, Sharon! They're Europeans!
这真是坨了不起的屎, Mr. Marsh. - 看在上帝的份上！
It is a tremendous crap, Mr. Marsh. - For the love of God!
你的粪便重达8.6卡里克 -卡里克？
Your crap officially weighs, 8.6 Courics. - Courics?
用来测量人类排泄物的国际标准单位
The standard measuring unit for human feces.
一卡里克大约等于2.5磅重量的便便
One Katie Couric is approximately two and a half pounds of excrement.
现在的纪录是一坨重7.5卡里克
The current record is a crap weighing 7.5 Courics.
这就是说... - 对了
But that means... - That's right.
你就是新的世界冠军! - 真滴吗?!
You are the new world's champion! - Really?!
你是说真滴吗?!
You mean, really?!
嘿 Stan! 嘿 Sharon! 嘿 各位!
Hey Stan! Hey Sharon! Hey everybody!
我想我们最好打个电话给老的世界纪录保持者
Well, I guess we'd better call the old champoin...
让他知道他的纪录刚才被打破了
and let him know his record has just been broken.
他赢过22座格莱美奖, 数不清的人道主义奖
He has won twenty-two Grammy's, countless humanitarian awards...
并且是世界上唯一一位同时赢得
and is the only person ever to be nominated for an Academy Award, a Golden Globe...
学院奖，金地球奖和诺贝尔和平奖的人 女士们先生们,欢迎 Bono!
and the Nobel Peace Prize. Ladies and gentlemen, Bono!
谢谢大家 谢谢大家 这对我来说太重要了
Thank you. Thank you so much for this newest award, it means so much.
对不起，肯定是又有人通知我去领奖了
Excuse me. I must be getting another award.
你好? - 你好, Bono
Yes? - Yes, Bono.
先生,我们特来告诉你，你所保持的世界上最大的屎的纪录 刚被打破了
Sir, we wish to inform you that your record for biggest crap has just been broken.
什么?! 这不可能! 新的纪录有多大?
What?! That's impossible! How big was it?
今天我们在这共同为首位获得欧洲人类排泄物协会
We are here to honor the first American...
颁发的世界上最大便便的奖章的美国人表示祝贺！
to bring home the distinguished EFSM medal for biggest crap ever taken.
嘿 看到了吗, Sharon, 那可是总统大人! 嘿 Sharon!
Hey look, Sharon, it's the President! Hey Sharon!
让我们欢迎颁奖嘉宾 欧洲人类排泄物协会的会长 Orloff Broloff先生
To present the award I give you the dean of the EFSM, Sir Orloff Broloff.
谢谢，议员先生 在超过一个世纪的时间里, 欧洲人类排泄物协会一直在-
Thank you, Senator. For over a hundred years, the European Fecal Standards and Meas-
Broloff先生! Broloff先生!
Herr Broloff! Herr Broloff!
是真的吗?
Das shpoitenhoff?
厄...女士们先生们
Ah ladies and gentlemen...
我们接受到一条最新消息，我们刚接到了一份 来自Bono先生的特制视频声明
I understand we have just received a special video-taped announcement from Bono!
Bono? 酷！
Bono? Cool!
请在大屏幕上播放这段视频?
Could we play the tape on the big screen, please?
各位好， 我是Bono.
Hello everyone! I, am Bono.
这几年来，为非洲寻求帮助和发展 已经成了我生命中的一部分
For years it has been my honor to try and bring focus to the needs in Africa.
今天，我有一个特别的消息带给大家
And today, I have very exciting news.
在昨晚大约8点20分的时候，我拉下了 一坨重达9.5卡里克的便便
Last night, at twenty past eight, I took a crap weighing nine and a half Courics.
Bono?!
正如你们所看到的, 这可是一整坨 这是我有史以来拉过的最大一坨
As you can see, it is one solid piece. It is my biggest crap to date.
我敢发誓它的真实性 谢谢各位，祝上帝保佑你们
And I swear to its authenticity. Thank you, and God bless.
你们都听见啦，女士们先生们! 目前最大的便便是9.5卡里克!
You heard it, ladies and gentlemen! The official biggest crap is 9.5 Courics!
一起祝贺Bono!
Congratulations to Bono!
爸爸，我想晚餐快好了哦
Dad, I think dinner's almost ready.
我差点就成功了
I almost did it.
我差点就凭自己的本事真正的做点什么
I almost made something of myself.
你知道吗，当你那么接近成功的时候，你甚至 会觉得，或许你的生活将走向不凡
You know, when you get real close, you start to think that maybe your life is gonna matter.
我意思是，这可是我真正的心血结晶啊
I mean, this was something I made!
从我身体里分离出来的，也是我身体的一部分啊
Something that came from me! That was a a part of me!
我这辈子做的唯一有意义的事情！
The only thing I ever made that was any good!
天啊，别想那么多了，老爸 - 谢谢你
Gee, thanks a lot, Dad. - You're welcome.
我只是...
And I just...
我知道在我以后的日子里，我可能再也 不会有如此这么接近成功的机会了
I know that this late in my life I'll never come so close to finally having meaning.
来吧，两位，烤宽面条已经做好了
Come on guys, lasagna's ready.
宽面条做好了
Oh. Lasagna's ready.
你听见了吗， Stan? 你妈说宽面条已经做好了!
You hear that, Stan? Mom says lasagna is ready!
我能听出你的讽刺意味, Sharon!
I can see through your sarcasm, Sharon!
你在说什么啊? - 你完全可以说, Sharon!
What are you talking about? - You can say it, Sharon!
我知道Bono比我好!
I know Bono's better than me!
很遗憾我不是Bono，满意了吧?!
I'm sorry I'm not Bono, all right?!
真对不起，我没有上亿的资产， 也没有诺贝尔奖提名！
Sorry that I don't have billions of dollars and a Nobel prize nomination!
Randy, 这真荒谬! - 哦，这可是我的真心话, Sharon!
Randy, this is ridiculous! - Oh, that's real mature, Sharon!
你就像什么事情都在搞笑一样! 这整件事对你来说就是个大笑话，是不是?!
Just act like everything's funny! It's a big joke to you, isn't it?!
就是一个笑话! 不要碰我!
Just a big joke! Don't touch me!
你能相信吗?! 这一切都只是为了谁拉的屎大！
Can you believe him?! All this over what guy took the biggest crap!
你不理解的, Mom. 你真的不理解
You don't understand, Mom. You just don't understand.
Wha? Wha?
他们怎么能只凭那个叫Bono寄来的一张照片就让他获胜?
How come they just let that Bono guy send a picture of his crap?
因为他是Bono, 这就是原因. -但是他可能伪造照片啊，这不公平!
Because he's Bono, that's why. - But he could have faked it. It isn't fair!
已经没办法了，他现在已经是记录保持者了，我啥都干不了
Doesn't matter. He's got the record now, there's nothing I can do.
哦，有件事你能做的!你可以再拉一次! - 什么?
Oh yes there is! You could do it again! - What?
你想，上次你甚至连要拉最大的屎这个念头都没有
Think about it. You weren't even trying to take the biggest crap last time.
想想你如果马力全开的话！
Imagine if you actually worked at it!
嘿，没错！
Hey. Hey that's right.
不，我不能再经历一次了，实在太痛苦了
No. I can't go through all that again. It's too much.
加油, Randy. 我打赌你可以轻松再拉坨那么大的屎!
Come on, Randy. I'll bet you can crap that big again easy!
加上正确的食谱和锻炼，你拉出的便便绝对没有极限！
With the right diet and training, who knows what you're capable of?
伙计们, 算了吧! 结束了! 那只是一次巧合! 我再也不能拉出那么大的便便了
Guys, forget it! It's over! It was a fluke crap, I'll never take one that big again!
结束了吗, Randy?! 我们可是都亲眼看过你那坨大便便的啊!
Is it over, Randy?! We all saw that crap you took!
这绝不只是巧合! 这是你身上的某种潜能，使你 创造了奇迹!
That was no fluke! There's something inside you that made you able to do it!
Randy, 你是有天赋的! 谁知道上帝为什么要给你这个天赋，但是他确实是给了！
Randy, you have a gift. Now who knows why God chose you, but he did!
如果你就这么放弃的话，你一辈子也不会知道...
And if you walk away now, you'll always wonder...
你能拉多大的便便
how big a crap you could have taken!
我可能需要很多的帮助 - 我们一切都乐意效劳！
I would need a lot of help. - That's what we're here for.
好吧, Randy, 你准备怎么办?!
Come on, Randy, what do you say?!
我想说...
I say...
让Bono知道我的厉害!
Let's give Bono a run for his money!
这里是CNN头条新闻.
This is CNN Headline News.
今晚，一场关于伊朗的军事打击...
Tonight, a possible attack on Iran...
可能意味着新的中东战争拉开序幕
may mean the beginning of a new war in the Middle East.
欧，不是吧
Oh no.
但是首先要说的是，世界上最大便便的纪录是不是 又会再次被破呢?
But first, the record for the world's biggest crap, will it again be broken?
科罗拉多的Randy Marsh为了挑战新的纪录 已经准备了三周的时间了
Randy Marsh of Colorado is now three weeks into his quest to make a new crap.
他把所有的日常时间都用于在P.F. Chang吃东西
Spending nearly every waking hour at P.F. Chang's.
这有什么新闻价值吗？
Is this really newsworthy?
你根本就不了解
You just don't understand.
是的，我不能理解
You're right. I don't.
同时, 一些人在质疑Bono纪录的真实性
At the same time, some people are questioning Bono's current record entry...
因为没有人亲眼看到那坨便便
saying nobody has ever seen it in person.
目前暂时联系不到Bono,因为他现在正在非洲
Bono could not be reached for comment, as he is currently in Africa helping the needy.
Hello, hello.
Marsh 正在准备打破那个纪录 我们想你应该知道这件事
Marsh is attempting to break the record again. We thought you should know.
他不可能击败我的9.5卡里克! - 他决定试试
He can't beat my nine and a half Courics! - Well he's going to try.
可以，但他必须在你面前拉下这泡屎！ 在苏黎世！
Fine, but he has to take the crap in front of you! In Zurich.
Bono, 我们以前从来没有这项规矩
Bono, we've never had that rule before.
这是唯一知道他没有作弊的办法！
I's the only way you can know he's not cheating!
如果他不是在苏黎世拉的话，那就不能算！
If he doesn't crap in Zurich, it shouldn't count!
超声检查是很简单的, Mr. Marsh.
Ultrasound is very simple, Mr. Marsh.
我们将用无害的超声波检查你的胃
We're going to use harmless waves to look inside your belly.
首先要在你的肚子上涂点防护油
Just gonna put some warm gel on your stomach first.
Ok, 深呼吸
Okay, take a deep breath.
我看见一坨屎了，我不能保证 但是我想它可能有
I see the crap now. I can't say for sure, but I, I'd say is about...
14卡里克 -14?!
14 Courics. - Fourteen?!
太棒了，Randy! - 我能看看嘛?
That's great, Randy! - Can I, Can I see it?
可以 这是你的盲肠，这里是你肚子里的那坨屎
Sure. This is your colon and here is the feces growing inside your belly.
伙计们，我们有个问题!
Guys, we have a problem!
刚和欧洲便便协会通过话 他们说Randy 必须去苏黎世拉这坨屎
I talked to the EFSM and they say Randy has to take the crap in Zurich.
苏黎世？
In Zurich?
他们说这是Bono要求的 他们也没办法
They say that Bono is demanding it and that their hands are tied.
对不起 Mr. Marsh, 以你目前的身体状况 坐飞机是非常不合适的
I'm sorry Mr. Marsh, I I cannot condone you traveling on an airplane in your condition.
在你粪便成型期，出行是非常不安全的
It is never safe to fly during your turd trimester.
Hi, 请问我能和Mr. Bono说几句话吗? - Mr. Bono, 您有位年轻的拜访者!
Hi, could I speak to Mr. Bono, please? - Mr. Bono, you have a young gentleman caller!
把喷气机准备好, Bovis! 我要走了
Get the jet ready, Bovis! I've got to be going.
Hi, 我的名字叫Stan Marsh 我父亲正向您的最大便便纪录发起挑战
Hi, my name is Stan Marsh. My dad's trying to beat your record for biggest crap.
哦，对的，他赶不到苏黎世了，是吗？
Oh right. He can't make it to Zurich, right?
这就是我到这里来的原因 这个最大便便的纪录，对你很重要吗？
That's kind of what I'm here for. Do you really need the biggest crap record?
请问您能稍微退让一下，让我爸爸获得这个头衔吗?
Could you maybe see your way to just letting my dad have this one?
让他获得? 为什么我要这么做?!
Let him have it? Why would I do that?!
先生，您得理解我们，我老爸 以前从来没赢过任何东西..
Look, you gotta understand, sir. My dad's never won an award for anything. Ever.
他从来就没有赢过任何一个奖项和奖杯
He doesn't have one single trophy.
甚至我都有个销售体育画报第二名的奖杯
I mean, even I have a second-place trophy for most Sports Illustrated subscriptions sold.
那是因为我拿了第一名
I have the first-place trophy for that.
伙计，难道你还不满足吗? 我意思是..
Dude, don't you have enough? I mean...
你有数不清的钱, 喷气式飞机，世界上最大的乐队 一个超性感的老婆
you got tons of money, a jet and the biggest rock band in the world, a hot wife and...
你甚至被授予了爵位.. 我意思是，在某些地方，你就不能让一让吗？
you've been knighted. I mean, at some point, can't you just kind of fuck off?
我要让大家都知道我的价值，我有多重要
I want people to know that I'm worth something. That I matter.
我只是要求仅在这么一件事上， 您可以让我爸爸当一次第一名
All I'm asking is that maybe with this one thing, let my dad be number 1.
你仍然可以当第二名啊
And you can still be number 2.
第二名?! 第二名?!
Number two?! Number two?!
谁都不能这么说我!
Nobody calls me that anymore and gets away with it!
把这话收回去! 把它收回去! - 我收回!
Take it back! Take it back! - I take it back!
说我不是第二名! - 你不是第二名!
Say I'm not number two! - You're not number two!
这还差不多，我才不是呢！
That's right! I'm not!
这家伙有什么病?
What is wrong with that guy?
你爸爸现在有危险，跟我来
Your father is in grave danger. Come with me!
这坨便便一定超大啊
It must be quite a crap.
加油, Randy，你必须使劲!
Come on, Randy. You have to push!
你在说什么?! 你怎么知道我爸爸会处于危险之中?!
What are you saying?! How do you know my dad is gonna die?!
因为从没有人能拉这么大的屎
Because nobody has ever taken a crap that big before!
那就是说Bono的新纪录确实是个谎言!
So Bono's newest record is a lie!
我最初发现事情不对劲的时候，是我发现了 Bono的首个最大便便的奖杯
Look, I first knew something was wrong when I looked at Bono's first award for biggest crap.
上面写着1960年颁发的奖杯 - 所以呢?
It said he took it in 1960. - So?
那一年Bono刚刚出生 然后我什么都明白了
So that's the year Bono was born. Then it all made sense to me.
为什么Bono能这么有才, 如此有爱心 可看上去依然和一坨屎没什么分别?
How could Bono be so talented, so caring and yet seem like such a piece of crap?
因为他本来就是一坨屎 你明白了吗? Bono根本不是什么纪录保持者
Because he is crap. Don't you get it? Bono is not the record holder...
他自己就是那个纪录 - 没错
He's the record. - Yes.
我做不到! 我做不到!
I can't do it! I can't do it!
这坨屎实在是太大了, Mr. Marsh. 我们必须剖开肚子把它取出来!
The crap is simply too big, Mr. Marsh. We must perform a Caesarean!
可那样的话，还能算数吗? - 不算!
But then, does it still count? - Oh, no!
最大的屎必须是你拉出来的! - 他说的没错
A biggest crap means you crapped it out! - I believe that's true.
很遗憾, Mr. Marsh, 但是如果不是你亲自拉出来的话
We are sorry, Mr. Marsh, but if you cannot crap out the crap...
那就不能算数
it's not really a crap.
No... No.
没事的，Randy. 你已经尽了最大努力了
There there Randy. You gave it your best shot.
我想见我的太太  Sharon? Sharon?
I want my wife. Sharon? Sharon?
什么?! - 对不起, Sharon.
What?! - I'm sorry, Sharon.
对不起让你失望了 对不起我没能赢Bono
I'm sorry that I let you down. I'm sorry I can't crap like Bono.
恭喜你了, Bono, 看来你的纪录依旧保持
Well congratulations, Bono, it appears your record is intact.
我早就知道是这样 - 等等！停一下！
I had a feeling it would be. - Wait! Stop!
爸爸，你以前那坨屎就应该赢了！ Bono从来没有拉过能赢你的那坨！
Dad, your old crap counts. Bono never took a second crap to beat yours.
把他赶出去！ - 你在说什么，年轻人?
Get him out of here! - What are you talking about, young man?
某人有个秘密，Bono从来就不是这个纪录的 保持者! 他就是那坨屎!
Somebody's been keeping it a secret. Bono was never the record holder! He's the record!
这不是真的! 杀了这个小孩! 我要他死!
It's not true! Kill the kid! I want him dead!
太晚了, Bono. 这个小男孩已经知道了真相
It's too late, Bono. The boy has learned the truth.
Broloff会长, 你关于这个知道什么? - 我恐怕那是真的
Herr Broloff, what do you know of this? - It's true, I'm afraid.
直到Mr. Marsh出现前， 我才是世上最大便便纪录的保持者
You see, until Mr. Marsh came along, I was the record holder for the biggest crap.
我在1960年拉的 那是我有生以来拉的最神奇的一坨屎
I took it back in 1960. It was the most amazing crap I'd ever taken.
不，爸爸，别再说了！
Poppa no! Say nothing more!
过来吧，我亲爱的孩子
Come to me, my darling precious child.
当我获得纪录后，我把那坨便便 带回了家
After I had broken the record I took the crap home.
我是如此的为它自豪，我决定留下它， 像照顾我自己的孩子一样照料它
I was so proud of it that I decided to keep it, to try and raise it like a child.
不要说了，爸爸，不要说了 - 这就是了，我亲爱的小便便
No Poppa. No Poppa. - There there, my little crap.
别哭了 这儿，想吸奶奶吗？
Don't cry. Here, do you want the biddy?
Does Bono want the biddy?
是的，他爱吸奶奶，不是吗?
Yes, he likes the biddy doesn't he?
我晕
Dude.
我把那坨屎放在办公室，给它营养 给它喂奶
I kept the crap in my office, nursed it, fed it biddy.
很快，它吸着奶奶长壮了，长大了!
And soon biddy made him strong. Biddy made him grow up!
甚至成为了我们这个时代最有影响力的人物之一 轻点，Bono，那会弄疼了我的奶奶
Into one of the most influential figures of our time.Easy Bono, that hurts the biddy.
奶奶
Biddy.
我的小便便完成了很多精彩的壮举
My little crap has accomplished many things.
但是他从来不能接受他自己其实是便便的事实 （美国俚语中，numer two有便便的意思）
But he could never shed the fact that he was really a number two.
所以他用他一生的时间和精力要当第一名， 在所有事情上
So he spent his life trying to be number one, in everything.
这就是他为什么在能完成那么多的事， 帮助那么多人后，
That's why he's able to do so much, try to help so many people...
可让人觉得依然不过是一坨屎
but still seem like such a piece of shit.
你的行为让我们神圣的协会有了污点，Broloff会长
You have blemished this noble society's good name, Herr Broloff.
我有吗?! 瞧瞧我当年拉的这坨屎！
Have I?! Look at the crap I took all those years ago!
Bono现在已经有6英尺高，重达80卡里克!
Bono is now almost six feet tall and over 80 Courics in weight!
无论你们怎么看，它依旧是记录!
No matter how you look at it, he is still the record!
欧，上帝啊，来了! 疼啊 疼 疼 疼 疼!
Oh God, here it comes! Oh, hot, hot, hot, hot!
疼 疼 疼 疼 疼 疼!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot! Hot! Hot!
我的上帝啊... - 这一定超过了100卡里克!
My God... - It must be over a hundred Courics!
爸爸，你还好吗？ - 恩
Dad, are you all right? - Yeah, I'm...
我很好! 感觉好多了
No, I'm good! Feel a lot better.
Mr. Marsh, 非常抱歉 如果你不介意的话
Mr. Marsh, we apologize and if it's okay with you...
请拿好早就应该属于你的奖杯
we would like to present you... your long overdue trophy.